https://www.propylon.com/terms-and-conditions/cookie-policy/

Home/Terms and conditions/Privacy and cookies
Privacy and cookies
Maja Jovanovic
2020-11-23T16:46:25+00:00
PRIVACY STATEMENTThank you for visiting Propylon’s website. As a technology company, we take electronic privacy very seriously. Our policy is to collect no personal information about you when you visit our sites, unless you affirmatively choose to make such information available to us.
COOKIE POLICYThis site uses cookies – small text files stored in your browser necessary for the proper functioning of the website. We use cookies to retain any browser preferences you may have set and provide us with anonymized tracking data for Google Analytics. As a rule, cookies will make your browsing experience better. However, you may prefer to disable cookies on this site and on others. The most effective way to do this is to disable cookies in your browser. We suggest consulting the Help section of your browser or taking a look at the About Cookies website which offers guidance for all modern browsers.
About this cookie policy
This Cookie Policy explains what cookies are and how we use them, the types of cookies we use i.e, the information we collect using cookies and how that information is used, and how to control the cookie preferences. For further information on how we use, store, and keep your personal data secure, see our Privacy Policy.
You can at any time change or withdraw your consent from the Cookie Declaration on our websiteLearn more about who we are, how you can contact us, and how we process personal data in our Privacy Policy.Your consent applies to the following domains: www.propylon.comYour current state: No consent given. Manage your consent.
We use cookies on our website to give you the most relevant experience by remembering your preferences and repeat visits. By clicking “Accept”, you consent to the use of ALL the cookies.
MANAGE MY SETTINGSI ACCEPT
What are cookies ?
Cookies are small text files that are used to store small pieces of information. They are stored on your device when the website is loaded on your browser. These cookies help us make the website function properly, make it more secure, provide better user experience, and understand how the website performs and to analyze what works and where it needs improvement.
How do we use cookies ?
As most of the online services, our website uses first-party and third-party cookies for several purposes. First-party cookies are mostly necessary for the website to function the right way, and they do not collect any of your personally identifiable data.
The third-party cookies used on our website are mainly for understanding how the website performs, how you interact with our website, keeping our services secure, providing advertisements that are relevant to you, and all in all providing you with a better and improved user experience and help speed up your future interactions with our website.
What types of cookies do we use ?
Essential: Some cookies are essential for you to be able to experience the full functionality of our site. They allow us to maintain user sessions and prevent any security threats. They do not collect or store any personal information. For example, these cookies allow you to log-in to your account and add products to your basket, and checkout securely.
Statistics: These cookies store information like the number of visitors to the website, the number of unique visitors, which pages of the website have been visited, the source of the visit, etc. These data help us understand and analyze how well the website performs and where it needs improvement.
Marketing: Our website displays advertisements. These cookies are used to personalize the advertisements that we show to you so that they are meaningful to you. These cookies also help us keep track of the efficiency of these ad campaigns.The information stored in these cookies may also be used by the third-party ad providers to show you ads on other websites on the browser as well.
Functional: These are the cookies that help certain non-essential functionalities on our website. These functionalities include embedding content like videos or sharing content of the website on social media platforms.
Preferences: These cookies help us store your settings and browsing preferences like language preferences so that you have a better and efficient experience on future visits to the website.CookieTypeDurationDescription__widgetsettingsPersistentThis cookie is set by Twitter - The cookie allows the visitor to share content from the website on to their Twitter profile._exposure_session12 weeksThis cookie is set to help display embedded brochure from exposure.co, publishing platform for photographers and visual storytellers_ga02 yearsThis cookie is installed by Google Analytics. The cookie is used to calculate visitor, session, camapign data and keep track of site usage for the site's analytics report. The cookies store information anonymously and assigns a randoly generated number to identify unique visitors._gat01 minuteThis cookies is installed by Google Universal Analytics to throttle the request rate to limit the colllection of data on high traffic sites._gid01 dayThis cookie is installed by Google Analytics. The cookie is used to store information of how visitors use a website and helps in creating an analytics report of how the wbsite is doing. The data collected including the number visitors, the source where they have come from, and the pages viisted in an anonymous form.1P_JAR04 weeksThis cookie is used to stores information about how the user uses the website, recent searches or any other interactions with advertisements before visiting the website. This information is used to provide the users with personalized advertisments.ANID12 yearscookielawinfo-checkbox-analyticsPersistent1 yearThis cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The purpose of this cookie is to check whether or not the user has given the consent to the usage of cookies under the category 'Analytics'.cookielawinfo-checkbox-marketingPersistent1 yearThis cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The purpose of this cookie is to check whether or not the user has given the consent to the usage of cookies under the category 'Marketing'.cookielawinfo-checkbox-necessaryPersistent1 yearThis cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The purpose of this cookie is to check whether or not the user has given the consent to the usage of cookies under the category 'Necessary'.cookielawinfo-checkbox-performancePersistent1 yearThis cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The purpose of this cookie is to check whether or not the user has given the consent to the usage of cookies under the category 'Performance'.cookielawinfo-checkbox-preferencesPersistent1 yearThis cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The purpose of this cookie is to check whether or not the user has given the consent to the usage of cookies under the category 'Preferences'.GPS030 minutesThis cookie is set by Youtube and registers a unique ID for tracking users based on their geographical locationIDE12 yearsUsed by Google DoubleClick and stores information about how the user uses the website and any other advertisement before visiting the website. This is used to present users with ads that are relevant to them according to the user profile.lang0This cookie is used to store the language preferences of a user to serve up content in that stored language the next time user visit the website.NID16 monthsThis cookie is used to a profile based on user's interest and display personalized ads to the users.timezone0This cookie is used to store the time preferences of a user.viewed_cookie_policy01 hourThe cookie is set by the GDPR Cookie Consent plugin and is used to store whether or not user has consented to the use of cookies. It does not store any personal data.VISITOR_INFO1_LIVE15 monthsThis cookie is set by Youtube. Used to track the information of the embedded YouTube videos on a website.YSC1This cookies is set by Youtube and is used to track the views of embedded videos.
How can I control the cookie preferences ?
Should you decide to change your preferences later through your browsing session, you can click on the “Privacy & Cookie Policy” tab on your screen. This will display the consent notice again enabling you to change your preferences or withdraw your consent entirely.
In addition to this, different browsers provide different methods to block and delete cookies used by websites. You can change the settings of your browser to block/delete the cookies. To find out more about how to manage and delete cookies, visit wikipedia.org, www.allaboutcookies.org.
HomeTerms and conditionsPrivacy and cookies
Articles
Featured
Insights
Success stories
Uncategorized
Recent Tweets Tweets by @PropylonUS
Follow Propylon on social media
Cookie ConsentWhen you use this website we use cookies which are necessary for the website to function correctly. In addition, we use cookies to derive insights from our visitors and provide social media features.
You can agree to the use of cookies for the optimal experience or you can manage the settings from the default. To find out more please read our Cookie policy.
Click I ACCEPT to consent to the use of all cookies on this site.
MANAGE MY SETTINGS I ACCEPTCookies
Close
Privacy Overview
This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may affect your browsing experience.
Necessary
Necessary
Always Enabled
Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
CookieTypeDurationDescriptioncookielawinfo-checkbox-analyticsPersistent1 yearThis cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The purpose of this cookie is to check whether or not the user has given the consent to the usage of cookies under the category 'Analytics'.cookielawinfo-checkbox-marketingPersistent1 yearThis cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The purpose of this cookie is to check whether or not the user has given the consent to the usage of cookies under the category 'Marketing'.cookielawinfo-checkbox-necessaryPersistent1 yearThis cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The purpose of this cookie is to check whether or not the user has given the consent to the usage of cookies under the category 'Necessary'.cookielawinfo-checkbox-performancePersistent1 yearThis cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The purpose of this cookie is to check whether or not the user has given the consent to the usage of cookies under the category 'Performance'.cookielawinfo-checkbox-preferencesPersistent1 yearThis cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The purpose of this cookie is to check whether or not the user has given the consent to the usage of cookies under the category 'Preferences'.viewed_cookie_policy01 hourThe cookie is set by the GDPR Cookie Consent plugin and is used to store whether or not user has consented to the use of cookies. It does not store any personal data.
Performance
performance
Performance cookies are used to understand and analyze the key performance indexes of the website which helps in delivering a better user experience for the visitors.
CookieTypeDurationDescription__widgetsettingsPersistentThis cookie is set by Twitter - The cookie allows the visitor to share content from the website on to their Twitter profile._gat01 minuteThis cookies is installed by Google Universal Analytics to throttle the request rate to limit the colllection of data on high traffic sites.YSC1This cookies is set by Youtube and is used to track the views of embedded videos.
Preferences
preferences
Preference cookies are used to store user preferences to provide content that is customized and convenient for the users, like the language of the website or the location of the visitor.
CookieTypeDurationDescriptionlang0This cookie is used to store the language preferences of a user to serve up content in that stored language the next time user visit the website.timezone0This cookie is used to store the time preferences of a user.
Marketing
marketing
Marketing cookies are used to provide visitors with relevant ads and marketing campaigns. These cookies track visitors across websites and collect information to provide customized ads.
CookieTypeDurationDescription_exposure_session12 weeksThis cookie is set to help display embedded brochure from exposure.co, publishing platform for photographers and visual storytellers1P_JAR04 weeksThis cookie is used to stores information about how the user uses the website, recent searches or any other interactions with advertisements before visiting the website. This information is used to provide the users with personalized advertisments.ANID12 yearsIDE12 yearsUsed by Google DoubleClick and stores information about how the user uses the website and any other advertisement before visiting the website. This is used to present users with ads that are relevant to them according to the user profile.NID16 monthsThis cookie is used to a profile based on user's interest and display personalized ads to the users.VISITOR_INFO1_LIVE15 monthsThis cookie is set by Youtube. Used to track the information of the embedded YouTube videos on a website.
Analytics
analytics
Analytical cookies are used to understand how visitors interact with the website. These cookies help provide information on metrics the number of visitors, bounce rate, traffic source, etc.
CookieTypeDurationDescription_ga02 yearsThis cookie is installed by Google Analytics. The cookie is used to calculate visitor, session, camapign data and keep track of site usage for the site's analytics report. The cookies store information anonymously and assigns a randoly generated number to identify unique visitors._gid01 dayThis cookie is installed by Google Analytics. The cookie is used to store information of how visitors use a website and helps in creating an analytics report of how the wbsite is doing. The data collected including the number visitors, the source where they have come from, and the pages viisted in an anonymous form.GPS030 minutesThis cookie is set by Youtube and registers a unique ID for tracking users based on their geographical location
Save & Accept
